<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">"Story Studio Pro"</string>
    <string name="open">Open Drawer</string>
    <string name="close">Closed Drawer</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="changelog"><![CDATA[<u>Changelog</u>]]></string>

    <string-array name="Madlibs">
        <item>Story Studio Pro</item>
        <item>Create Your Own</item>
        <item>Saved Stories</item>
        <item>Settings</item>
        <item>About</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="MadlibsStories">
        <item>One day, when I was at school, I caught the _ from a _ boy named _. My sickness caused my _ to swell to the size of a balloon. I pee\'d out _. I coughed up _ egg\'s. All I would eat was _. After my _ found out I was sick, she made me wear a _ _ over my _ for _ weeks. </item>
        <item>Once upon a time there lived a family of _ who lived in a _ on a tall _ in the country. One _ day, the _ noticed a _ looking _ parked outside near their barn, for days it would _ there with _ curtains covering the windows. One night, he decided to take a _. He looked around and suddenly the back door slammed _ and _ _ in _ _ masks jumped out and held a _ to his throat. They all started _ over to the house and kicked down the _. The family _ bit one of the intruders _ and ripped their _. Before the _ could reach the _, they tied her to a _ and wrapped _ around her _. The young _ ran to the _ to get a _, hid behind the _ and _. She _ out at one of the intruders and slit their _ _ times over and over again and ran for the _ to call the _. As they were on their way, she stabbed another intruder in the _ as he tried to steal their _, but she slipped and fell on her _ when she hit her head on the _. When police arrived, the family was _ and they were told that the _ guys were originally from _ looking for _ to steal from families. The family was awarded a hefty _ dollar reward and _ free tickets to the Walkers _ House.</item>
        <item><![CDATA[The snow glows white on the _ tonight<br />Not a _ to be seen<br />A kingdom of isolation,<br />And it looks like I\'m the Queen.<br />The wind is howling like this _ _ inside<br />Couldn\'t keep it in, heaven knows I tried<br /><br />Don\'t let them in, don\'t let them see<br />Be the _ girl you always have to be<br />Conceal, don\'t feel, don\'t let them know<br />Well, now they know<br /><br />Let it go, let it go<br />Can\'t hold it back anymore<br />Let it go, let it go<br />Turn away and _ the _<br /><br />I don\'t care<br />What they\'re going to say<br />Let the _ rage on,<br />The cold never bothered me anyway<br /><br />It\'s funny how some distance<br />Makes everything seem _<br />And the fears that once controlled me<br />Can\'t get to me at all<br /><br />It\'s time to see what I can do<br />To test the limits and break _<br />No right, no wrong, no rules for me<br />I\'m free<br /><br />Let it go, let it go<br />I am one with the wind and sky<br />Let it go, let it go<br />You\'ll never see me _<br /><br />Here I stand<br />And here I\'ll stay<br />Let the storm rage on<br /><br />My power flurries through the air into the ground<br />My soul is spiraling in frozen _ all around<br />And one thought crystallizes like an icy blast<br />I\'m never going back,<br />The past is in the past<br /><br />Let it go, let it go<br />And I\'ll rise like the break of dawn<br />Let it go, let it go<br />That _ girl is gone<br /><br />Here I stand<br />In the light of day<br />Let the storm rage on,<br />The _ never bothered me anyway]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[Prince Adam was cursed to a beast form by an Enchantress who saw no love in his _ _ for others. The one way he could break the spell was to learn to love another and earn her love in return before the last _ from his enchanted _ fell, which would last until his twenty-first birthday. But who could ever learn to love a beast?<br /><br />Ten years later, Maurice, a _ inventor from a _ village, becomes lost in the woods and seeks shelter in the Beast\'s castle, the Beast _ him for trespassing. His daughter Belle, a bookworm who dreams of life outside her _ village, finds him trapped in the castle and offers her place in his stead. The Beast accepts with a promise she\'ll remain in the castle forever.<br /><br />In the beginning Belle views him as nothing more than a _, he views her as difficult and _. But the two soon taste the bitter-sweetness of finding you can change and learning you were _.]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[One morning, Dora awoke with a _ smile on her _. Her best friend, Boots the monkey, was coming over to play. And, he was going to bring a _ surprise!<br /><br />Dora was so excited, she accidentally brushed her teeth with _ instead of _ tooth-paste. _! _ Dora!<br /><br />Before Boots arrived, Dora wanted to make him his favorite snack: _ bananas on toast. But, when she checked her kitchen, she couldn\'t find any bananas.<br /><br />\'Oh _\', thought Dora. This is _!<br /><br />Suddenly, Dora remembered that bananas grow on trees. _ thinking, Dora!<br /><br />But, Dora didn\'t have any banana trees near her house. So, she decided to use the _ fruit of the _ trees that grew in her _ instead.<br /><br />_, Dora exclaimed when the snacks were ready. \'These taste just like _.<br /><br />Just then, Dora heard a familiar knock at her door. Boots had come! Dora was so happy she almost jumped on the floor.<br /><br />\'Dora!\' Boots exclaimed.<br /><br />\'Hola, Boots...\' Dora said. \'Is this my surprise\'<br /><br />A new friend was standing next to Boots!<br /><br />\'Yes...\' said Boots. \'This is _ from _. We\'ve been playing all sorts of _ games\'<br /><br />\'_,\' said Dora, \'this is the best suprise I\'ve gotten in _ months\'<br /><br />The three friends spent the rest of the day together. They played with _ in the forest and built gigantic forts made out of _. Dora got to learn lots of new games, too. She even won at chase the _.<br /><br />In the evening, Dora shared her _ snacks. Boots giggled and said they tasted like _. Everybody thought they were _.<br /><br />When all the treats were gone, everyone piled on to the _ to cuddle. They all agreed that they\'d just had the most _ day ever!]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[To my Dearest _<br /><br />I cannot contain my _ that today is our wedding day!<br />It seems like only yesterday when I first saw your _ _. I could not believe how _ you were, and today I am the luckiest _ alive. You are _, _, and _, and I couldn\'t ask for anything more. The way you _ melts my heart. I want you to know that I will do all I can to give you a _ life. My job as a _ may not seem like much, but we will be rich with _, _, and _. One day we will have _ _ children. I hope that they have my _ and your _ _ and _. When I see you walk down the aisle today I know I will _ with joy! I love you with all my _.<br /><br />Love, <br /><br />_]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[I _ up this morning with a huge _. I went _ to find that my living room was a _. Beer _ and _ left _ were all _ the place. My dog _ on the couch and two of my gay friends passed out in my _ yard. The _ was playing _ songs and my tv\'s screen was _ in a half. There was a _ in my bath tub and a drunk squirrel outside by the swing. I went back upstairs and _ a note on my _ saying. One hella of a night chika. The question to this day still remains. What really did happen?]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[Dear _<br /><br />I have been having such a _ time. I\'m glad you talked me into going. There is always something new to _ everyday, and new people to _. Today for lunch, we had _ from the grill, and chocolate _. It was so good! I made a friend at lunch, named _. She has asthma, so she\'s not allowed to _ some of the activities that the rest of us _. I want to _ her so bad, but I don\'t know what to do. If you could send me some _ I think I will give her some, so she will feel better. I will be _ you next week, when you pick me up. Love you always,<br /><br />Your little girl,<br /><br /><br />_<br /><br />P S. Have some _ waiting for me when I get home. You know I love the _ ones. Bye for now.]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[The story opens with the unrestrained celebration of a _ wizarding world which for many years had been terrorised by Lord Voldemort. The previous night, Voldemort had discovered the refuge of the hidden Potter family, killed _ and James Potter. However, when he attempted to kill Harry, the Avada Kedavra _ curse rebounded upon him, and Voldemort was destroyed, becoming nothing more than a _: neither dead nor alive. Harry, meanwhile, was left with a distinctive lightning bolt-shaped scar on his _ the only physical sign of Voldemort\'s curse. Harry\'s _ defeat of Voldemort results in him being dubbed \'The Boy Who Lived\' by the wizarding community.<br /><br />The following night, a wizard named _ delivers Harry to what will be his residence for many years afterward. The orphaned Harry is subsequently _ by his cruel, non-magical relatives, the Dursleys, who in attempt to rid him of his magical _ hide his magical heritage and give him severe punishments after several strange occurrences.<br /><br />However, as his eleventh birthday approaches, Harry has his first contact with the magical world when he receives _ from _ School of Witchcraft and Wizardry, which are taken from him by his Aunt and Uncle before he has a chance to read them. On his eleventh birthday he is informed by Hagrid, the _ of Hogwarts, that he is in fact a _ and has been invited to attend Hogwarts. Each book chronicles one year in Harry\'s life, which is mostly spent at Hogwarts, where he learns to use _ and _ _. Harry also learns to overcome many magical, social, and _ obstacles as he struggles through his adolescence, Voldemort\'s rise to power and the Ministry of Magic\'s consistent denials of Voldemort\'s threat for a whole _.]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[I\'ll never forget the time I ate _ magic mushrooms! My friend _ turned into a _. We flew over _ on a _ _! I was seeing _ and green _ everywhere. We decided to go skiing on a _ mountain called the _ _. We later joined a _ fan club but everyone turned into _. We were surrounded but escaped _ with the help of a _ _. I know crazy _ he shouted. After hours of _ everything was back to normal but then I saw _ _ to a _ orchestra. _ I cried out]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[Hey this is _ Mays here with Oxi _. It makes your whites _ and your brights _. It gets _ wine and _ juice out of white carpets. Don\'t just clean, Oxi _. Call in the next _ minutes and you will also _ a _ bottle! Just one _ in each load and it makes your whites _. But wait there is more, call now and you will recieve another _ for half the price. So all that for...not 5, not 4, no, not even 3, but _ _ payments of $_. Here is how to _. Call 1-800-555-5555.]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[Congratulations! You finally managed to get a job interview at _. Follow these _ steps and you\'ll be _ for sure!<br /><br />1 ) Make sure you dress appropriately. You should probably wear something like a _ _. Make sure it\'s not too _ or _. Prospective employers do not like to see too much _.<br /><br />2 ) Be sure to _ and _ your _ before the interview. Make sure your breath is _<br /><br />3 ) Smile, be _ and remember a firm _ shake is always a plus!<br /><br />4 ) Make sure to mention such topics as _ _ and _. Be sure to avoid talking about _. They might get the wrong impression and think you are too _.<br /><br />5 ) You may want to compliment your potential boss on his/her _ and mention how much you enjoyed _ with them.<br /><br />6 ) Get plenty of _ the night before the interview and don\'t _ too much and you will do fine!]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[You\'re _ don\'t know what for<br /><br />You\'re turning heads when you _ through the do-o-or<br /><br />Don\'t need make-up - to cover up<br /><br />Being the way that you are is eno-o-ough<br /><br />Everyone else in the _ can see it<br /><br />Everyone else but yo-ou<br /><br />Baby you light up my world like nobody else<br /><br />The way that you _ your _ gets me overwhelmed<br /><br />But when you smile at the ground, it ain\'t hard to tell<br /><br />You don\'t know<br /><br />Oh oh<br /><br />You don\'t know you\'re _<br /><br />If only you saw what I can see<br /><br />You\'ll understand why I want you so desperatley<br /><br />Right now I\'m _ at you and I can\'t believe<br /><br />You don\'t know<br /><br />Oh oh<br /><br />You don\'t know you\'re _<br /><br />Oh oh<br /><br />That\'s what makes you _<br /><br />So c-come on, you got it _<br /><br />To prove I\'m _ I put it in a so-o-ong<br /><br />I don\'t know why, you\'re being _<br /><br />And turn away when I look in to your eye eye eyes<br /><br />Everyone else in the _ can see it<br /><br />Everyone else but yo-ou<br /><br />Baby you light up my world like nobody else<br /><br />The way that you _ your _ gets me overwhelmed<br /><br />But when you smile at the ground, it ain\'t hard to tell<br /><br />You don\'t know<br /><br />Oh ohYou don\'t know you\'re _<br /><br />If only you saw what I can see<br /><br />You\'ll understand why I want you so desperatley<br /><br />Right now I\'m looking at you and I can\'t believe<br /><br />You don\'t know<br /><br />Oh oh<br /><br />You don\'t know you\'re _<br /><br />Oh oh<br /><br />That\'s what makes you _<br /><br />Na na na na na na naaaa na na,<br /><br />Na na na na na na.<br /><br />Na na na na na na naaaa na na,<br /><br />Na na na na na na.<br /><br />Baby you light up my world like nobody else<br /><br />The way that you _ you\'re _ gets me overwhelmed<br /><br />But when you smile at the ground, it ain\'t hard to tell<br /><br />You don\'t know<br /><br />Oh oh<br /><br />You don\'t know you\'re _<br /><br />Baby you light up my world like nobody else<br /><br />The way that you _ your _ gets me overwhelmed<br /><br />But when you smile at the ground, it ain\'t hard to tell<br /><br />You don\'t know<br /><br />No Oh oh<br /><br />You don\'t know you\'re _<br /><br />If only you saw what I can see<br /><br />You\'ll understand why I want you so desperatley<br /><br />Right now I\'m _ at you and I can\'t believe<br /><br />You don\'t know<br /><br />No Oh oh<br /><br />You don\'t know you\'re _<br /><br />No Oh oh<br /><br />You don\'t know you\'re _<br /><br />No Oh oh<br /><br />That\'s what makes you _.]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[About three things I was absolutely positive.<br /><br />First, _ was a _.<br /><br />Second, there was a _ of him and I didn\'t know how _ that _ might be that thirsted for my _.<br /><br />And third, I was _ and _ in love with _.]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[I walked up to that scary _ house to find the frisbee we had tossed over the _. My friends said that it was fine, but I wasn\'t sure. I saw a _ _ run through the yard and the _ creaked when I _ on them. As I knocked on the door, I got even more frightened because there were _ everywhere. It opened by itself, so I _ in. It seemed like one of those _ movies. I shouted, "Is anyone here? I need to find my frisbee."<br /><br />The door then _ loudly. I tried to open it, but I couldn\'t. It was too _ to see anything, so I just _ there for a _ and waited for something to happen. A _ came from around the _ and floated toward me. I backed away and tripped over a _. The _ handed me my frisbee and opened the _. It didn\'t make sense to me, but I was scared so I grabbed it and ran to my _. I never looked back as we _ away.]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[When I became a rockstar, I was in a band with my _ best friends _ and _.<br /><br />When I became a rockstar, we aways opened up with our hit song _.<br /><br />When I became a rockstar, we celebrated by going to _ and singing our other hit song _ all day long for _ hours straight!<br /><br />When I became a rockstar, I finally got to meet my idol _ and we went to _ together.<br /><br />When I became a rockstar, our manager _ hooked us up with the _ gig ever at _.<br /><br />When I became a rockstar, I couldn\'t be more _ then I was!]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[1. Get 2 slices of _ bread<br /><br />2. Get _ pickles and SLAM \'em on that bread<br /><br />3. Use a blender to blend some _ olives with some _ mayonnaise to make a _ spread.<br /><br />4. Enjoy Your _ Sandwich!]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[In the _ Land of _, a _ new creature was discovered. It had _ _, and a _ coat of _. They are very rare, found only on a _ island to the _. They are very _, often _ away from _. Only _ are left in the whole world. They are related to _.]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[The _ _ _ went up the _ spout.<br /><br />Down came the _ and _ the spider out.<br /><br />Out came the _ and dried up all the _.<br /><br />And the _ _ _ went up the spout again.]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[HEAD KNIGHT OF NI: _<br /><br />KNIGHTS OF NI: _<br /><br />ARTHUR: Who are you?HEAD KNIGHT: We are the _ who say _<br /><br />Knights: _<br /><br />ARTHUR: No! Not the _ Who Say _<br /><br />HEAD KNIGHT: The same!<br /><br />BEDEVERE: Who are they?<br /><br />HEAD KNIGHT: We are the keepers of the _ words: _ _ and _<br /><br />Knights: _<br /><br />ARTHUR: Those who _ them seldom live to tell the tale.<br /><br />HEAD KNIGHT: The _ Who Say _, demand a sacrifice.<br /><br />ARTHUR: _ of _ we are but _ travelers who seek the _ who lives beyond these woods.<br /><br />HEAD KNIGHT: _<br /><br />KNIGHTS: _<br /><br />ARTHUR: Ow! Agh!<br /><br />HEAD KNIGHT: We shall say _, again to you if you do not appease us.<br /><br />ARTHUR: Well, what is it you want?<br /><br />HEAD KNIGHT: We want. a _<br /><br />ARTHUR: A what?<br /><br />KNIGHTS: _<br /><br />ARTHUR and PARTY: Ow! Oh!<br /><br />ARTHUR: Please! Please! No more! We will find you a _.<br /><br />HEAD KNIGHT: You must return here with a _ or else, you will never pass through this wood. Alive.<br /><br />ARTHUR: O _ of _ you are _ and _ and we will return with a _.<br /><br />HEAD KNIGHT: One that looks _.<br /><br />ARTHUR: Of course.<br /><br />HEAD KNIGHT: And not too _.<br /><br />ARTHUR: Yes.<br /><br />HEAD KNIGHT: Now. go!]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[I let it _ my _<br /><br />And as it _ you _ to _ it<br /><br />It was _ and I was _<br /><br />Until you _ my _ and you _ me<br /><br />My _ they were _<br /><br />But my _ were far too _<br /><br />To _ in your _ without _ to your _<br /><br />But there\'s a _ to you that I never _ never _<br /><br />All the _ you\'d _ they were never _ never _<br /><br />And the _ you\'d _ you would always _ always _<br /><br />But I set fire to the _<br /><br />Watched it _ as I _ your _<br /><br />Well, it _ while I _<br /><br />\'Cause I heard it _ out your _<br /><br />Your _.]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[It had been a _ day. The sky was dark and _ looking. The air was _ but so quiet that you could hear a _ drop. The weatherman on the _ weather station said that conditions were favorable for tornadoes in the _ area to develop. He warned the people of the _ town to stay tuned and to listen for directions in case something _ happened. After listening to the forecast, the farmer ran to his barn and saddled up his _ horse. He had to go out to the pasture and round up his _ and get them to the safety of the barn. He knew it was _ but he had to protect his _ animals. The _ were worth _ dollars each. He was only in the field for _ minutes when he realized that he made a _ mistake. The storm was moving faster than he thought it would. It was travelling at _ miles per hour. The sky looked as if it had been _. To the east it was bright and _, but in the west the sky was dark with _ looking clouds. When he found his _ by their _ they stared at him as if they did not know what to do. When the funnel saw the _ looking funnel closing in on him, his horse got _ and ran off to the safety of the barn. The funnel _ dropped to the ground and the farmer ran to his _ and laid down flat beside it. The tornado turned around _ and got very close to him. He saw something out of the corner of his eye flying through the air. A _ flew out of the tornado and hit his head and knocked him out. He woke up _ minutes later. He felt _ and his head hurt. A _ vet _ shook him to wake him up. The farmer finally recognized him. The vet checks his animals for _ diseases two times per month. The farmer told him to go get help. The farm was badly damaged. Luckily, he had _ insurance and was alive.]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[I was home alone and scared out of my _. I could hear the wind _ and off in the distance a _ was howling. I crossed the room, locked the _ and I climbed into bed; I pulled the _ over my _. Then it happened. I could hear a _ _ up the _ stairs. My _ started to chatter and my _ were _. The _ was thrust open and there was a huge _ with hair all over its _. It was my father. \"Hi, we\'re home, \" he said _. \"Hope you weren\'t afraid of staying home alone?\" \"No,\" I said, lying through my _.]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[_ is in bloom,<br /><br />The PR transmissions will resume<br /><br />They\'ll try to _ _ that keep us all _ down<br /><br />And hope that we will never see the _ around<br /><br />( So come on )<br /><br />Another promise, another _<br /><br />Another packaged lie to keep us trapped in _<br /><br />And all the _ _ _ around our minds<br /><br />And endless red _ to keep the truth _<br /><br />( So come on )<br /><br />They will not _ us<br /><br />They will stop degrading us<br /><br />They will not _ us<br /><br />We will be _. So come on<br /><br />_ mind control<br /><br />Come let the revolution takes its toll<br /><br />If you could flick the _ and open your third _<br /><br />You\'d see that we should never _ afraid to die<br /><br />( So come on )<br /><br />_ up and _ the power back<br /><br />It\'s time the fat _ had a heart attack<br /><br />You know that their time\'s coming to an end<br /><br />We have to _ and watch our _ ascend<br /><br />( So come on )<br /><br />They will not _ us<br /><br />They will stop _ us<br /><br />They will not control us<br /><br />We will be _<br /><br />So come on<br /><br />Hey, hey, hey, hey<br /><br />Hey, hey, hey, hey<br /><br />Hey, hey, hey, hey<br /><br />They will not _ us<br /><br />They will stop _ us<br /><br />They will not _ us<br /><br />We will be _<br /><br />So _ on!]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[My friends and I decided to take a break from _ and go on a road trip to _. It was to be a _ adventure! With our backpacks full of _ and _, we headed to the nearest _ so we could rent a _. We drove for _, stopped off for a _ break and finally reached _ to get some sleep. The next morning we hiked up a _ trail and met some really _ people who taught us how to _, we ended up staying for _ and then made our way back on the road. It started _ so we knew a storm was coming; we had to _ our way to the nearest _. Before we knew it, it was raining _ and _. We all hitched a ride on the back of a _ until the _ stopped. We dried off at a _ store and freshened up in their _. Then I noticed I left my bag behind! We needed our _! We were so _ that we ended up having to buy some at the _ across the street. After a _ picnic by the _, we asked a _ man if we could borrow his _ so we could get to the next town. He _ said _. The ride was _, we saw _ and _ along the way, we even picked up a _ who offered us _! It was a _ trip!]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[This survey is all about you.<br /><br />-FAVORITES-<br /><br />1) Favorite color: _ <br /><br />2) Favorite TV show: The _ Diaries. <br /><br />3) Favorite food: _ chops with mashed _ and _ <br /><br />4) Favorite fast food: _ - Especially their famous _ <br /><br />5) Favorite shampoo: _ brand (the extra _ kind)<br /><br />6) Favorite music: Anything by _ (I like _ music)<br /><br />7) Favorite thing to do: _. I also like _.<br /><br />-WHEN WAS THE LAST TIME YOU-<br /><br />8) The last time you ate _ and _: _ <br /><br />9) The last time you _ someone: Last _ <br /><br />10) The last time you gave someone a _, just because you wanted to: _ ago <br /><br />11) The last time you won something: This _! I won a giant _ at _<br /><br />12) The last time you went _: _, with my _ <br /><br />13) The last time you got _: A few days ago at my _. <br /><br />-WHAT IS...-<br /><br />14) Your hair color: I\'m naturally _<br /><br />15) Your best friend\'s name: _ (I call him/her _ or _ for short)<br /><br />16) Your must-have item in your bag: A _ and definitely my _<br /><br />17) Your favorite quote: \"The best and most _ things in the world cannot be _ or even _, they must be felt with the _.\"<br /><br />18) Your most desired occupation: I\'d help rescue _! Nothing is more _ than a _ deed done _ <br /><br />Thank you for taking this survey!]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[I live on a _ farm with my _. We get up every day at _ o\'clock to the sound of our _ _. We feed the _, collect a handful of _ _ eggs, _ the _, milk the _ and lay down some _ for the horses. We also have a pen of _ _ and a bunch of goats for making the best tasting _! Last week, our chicken named _ had baby _, a whole _ of them! My _ sells specialty _ _ and _-grown turkeys during the holidays, everyone loves them! He also lets me drive the _ which is most fun, I take my dog with me who\'s a half poodle and half _ and he loves it! When relatives stay over, we all go _-back _ and _ picking. There is so much to do on a farm when you\'re _. Some days are hectic, but most days are _!]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[Today, you are going to learn how to become a great swimmer!<br /><br />First, you need a _. Make sure it\'s comfortable and not _. First lets start out at the _ end of the pool. Dip your _ in the _ until you\'re completely _. Then once you\'re in, start with the _ paddle. Kick your _ and _ like you\'re whipping _. You should start to float, if not, _ your muscles and try again. Once you\'re body is _ freely, lift your left _ and place it in front of your _. Then do the same with your right _. At the same time, kick your _ like you\'re a _ trying to _. You should see your body starting to move _, keep your _ in the air at all times and wearing some _ can protect your _. _ and _ - plugs are optional as well. Swim a few strokes around the _ until you get the hang of it. Next, we can try diving off the _. Pretend you\'re an _ flying freely through the _. It\'s a lot of fun! Once you go under water, remember to kick but stay _. Soon, you\'ll be able to float on _ without effort. Swimming is _, _ and _. I hope this step-by-step guide helped you become the _ swimmer!]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[We have sent you this _ to show our _. We are going to invade planet earth. We will strike at any time. So start focusing on your security. We will scare everyone with _. We will invade and take over the _ by _. You can\’t stop us, neither can _ or _; even _ can\’t! You can\’t do anything to stop us, except beating us up with a _. We shall defeat you, _ then dance around like a _ _. Prepare to be humiliated by our amazing force of _. We will invade in a surprising way! So beware of me the incredible _ alien and my great force. We will first attack _ then we will move north. You can use you\’re _ as a shield but it will be nothing compared to our _ force. _ will strike with all our force. Once you see our force, you will probably be _. It\’s probably because we are _, _, and _. I will be _ my beautiful force while you will be crying with fear _ remember we will not have any mercy. The _ have no fear against you. We will not stop at any _ since we have a space ship. We will _ defeat you. Good luck, but not really.]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[On a _ and _ summer day, two friends decided to go to the _. They packed up a basket full of _ and a bag full of _ and off they _. When they got to the beach, they saw it was very _. They were lucky to get a spot on the sand right next to the _. The two friends had a wonderful time _ in the water, _ sand castles, and _ in the warm summer sun. Soon it was time to go home. The two friends got ice cream cones and agreed that it was the _ day at the beach ever.]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[In the beginning of time in a _, two _ were sailing near an inlet near New Jersey. A pirate named Danell _ that his _ were getting _. His pirate friend Michael said yo ho, we have hit a _ and we have _ a leak. The water began to fill the boat _ and the pirates were _ they would sink and be eaten by _ sharks. The sharks began circling the _. The two pirates had to think _. "What should we do," said Danell. "I have _ and nails we could try to _ the boat with" said Michael. Danell agreed and they got to work, soon they had _ up the boat. Just then a _ ran into the boat and broke open the patch they had just finished. Without enough wood to fix it again, their fate looked grim. All of a sudden a school of giant prehistoric _ came _ by. They swam under the boat and _ it up to the surface so that it wouldn\'t sink. Jellyfish floated the boat all the way back into the _ and the _ pirates were saved.]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[]]></item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="MadlibsTitles">
        <item>School Sickness</item>
        <item>Intruders</item>
        <item>Let it Go: Frozen</item>
        <item>Beauty and the Beast</item>
        <item>Dora\'s Surprise</item>
        <item>A Letter to the Bride</item>
        <item>What Happened Last Night?</item>
        <item>Letter Home From Camp</item>
        <item>Harry Potter Story</item>
        <item>Magic Mushrooms</item>
        <item>Oxi Clean</item>
        <item>Job Interview</item>
        <item>One Direction: What Makes You Beautiful</item>
        <item>Twilight Synopsis</item>
        <item>Scary Encounter</item>
        <item>Rockstar</item>
        <item>Making a Sandwich</item>
        <item>New Creature</item>
        <item>Itsy Bitsy Spider</item>
        <item>Knights of Ni (Monty Python)</item>
        <item>Set Fire to the Rain - Adele</item>
        <item>Farmyard Storm</item>
        <item>The Dark</item>
        <item>Uprising - Muse</item>
        <item>A Road Trip</item>
        <item>Survey</item>
        <item>Life on the Farm</item>
        <item>Swimming Lessons</item>
        <item>Attacked by Aliens</item>
        <item>Day at the Beach</item>
        <item>Pirates</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="list">
        <item>20</item>
        <item>22 (Default)</item>
        <item>24</item>
        <item>26</item>
        <item>28</item>
        <item>30</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="LValues">
        <item>20</item>
        <item>22</item>
        <item>24</item>
        <item>26</item>
        <item>28</item>
        <item>30</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="list0">
        <item>Blue (Default)</item>
        <item>Light Grey</item>
        <item>Dark Grey</item>
        <item>Red</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="LValues0">
        <item>Blue</item>
        <item>LGrey</item>
        <item>DGrey</item>
        <item>Red</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>